What,
you actually developed
feelings for Gao Yuhai?
You really treat him as your master?
Song Yanfei,
don't think I don't know.
You're just using me.
You said it was for the stage,
but it's actually for revenge, isn't it?
I know.
You're Song Yucheng's son.
Seems you're quite a smart dog.
Yeah,
I am Song Yucheng's son.
Do you have proof?
You made me provide Mr. Gao's schedule
and help you humiliate Shen Xi.
Wasn't your goal to drive her crazy,
and then have her intentionally
run over Gao Yuhai?
So what?
Go call the police.
Have them arrest me.
I...
Feng Shu,
don't forget.
You raped Shen Xi,
and exploited
so many girls with Gao Yuhai.
I have proof of all of it.
And you?
Do you think the police will believe you
if you frame me?
So,
like I said,
we cooperate
and get what we both need.
Get what we need, my ass.
Gao Yayan ignores me completely.
She only likes you.
What if I disappear?
I'll go to Beijing,
Shanghai,
or anywhere she can't find me.
Then what are you
going to do?
Good question.
Next,
I need you to actually frame me.
I have to get dirty first
to blend into the darkness.
When I saw my dad's
lifelong hard work
destroyed just like that,
watching those enemies
toasting and thriving
in his
former office,
that's when you realize
dreams and
promises are
all bullshit.
They are nothing
compared to hatred.
I want Gao Yuhai dead.
From that day on,
I started preparing for this plan.
But I was
just a stray dog.
My dad
and my mom
were both gone.
And Gao Yuhai was worlds away from me.
How could I even get close to him?
I had to constantly switch sides,
using different circles to approach
and understand him,
so I could have a chance.
Until
I met Gao Yayan.
After I met her,
she quickly confessed
our relationship to her dad.
That old fox
sent someone to investigate me.
Song Yanfei's father
is Song Yucheng.
He's smart.
He knew I approached his daughter
with bad intentions,
so he made Yayan leave me.
But fortunately,
Yayan believes me.
Why do I have a father like you?
Ya Yan was willing to go against her dad
for me.
So I thought,
as long as I stay by her side,
I'll have a chance to strike.
Later,
I met
Feng Shu.
He wanted to marry into a wealthy family.
And me?
I just wanted to avenge my father.
So it was a piece of cake for me
to handle him.
If I remember correctly,
Feng Shu was the first one to report you.
I arranged it.
But later I realized
he was becoming less and less useful
to me.
Until
I met Shen Xi.
I did know that
Shen Xi was
forced to sleep with
Feng Shu and Gao Yuhai.
I did know that
I thought
she did it for me,
so I could accept it.
But when those
dirty things actually happened, I
found I couldn't.
I felt she was dirty.
I truly felt she was dirty.
You felt she was dirty?
Aren't you dirty?
With all the things you've done,
aren't you dirty?
Aren't you dirty?
I am dirty.
When my dad was forced to jump
off a building by Gao Yuhai,
was he dirty?
Those employees whose families were ruined
because my dad's company went bankrupt,
were they dirty?
Did Bai Jiuzhou deserve to die?
And those girls,
when they were forced
to sleep with Gao Yuhai,
were they dirty?
I am dirty.
I just wanted him dead.
Not only did I want him dead,
but I also wanted to marry
his daughter.
I transferred his assets to my name
and left him with nothing.
I also wanted to leave
his corpse in the wilderness.
I wanted to dig up his grave.
I am dirty.
Speaking of this...
Ya Yan
once agreed to
an engagement ceremony with Feng Shu.
No way.
What did that mean?
It meant I was going to be
out of the picture.
My revenge plan would be ruined.
Unacceptable.
I would never allow that to happen.
Have you ever thought about
why Gao Yayan
held such a grand
engagement ceremony with Feng Shu
and invited so many media outlets?
How would I know?
She had no source of income.
What else could she do?
You will never guess
why my father opposed
my relationship with Song Yanfei.
Because Song Yanfei
is Song Yucheng's son.
And eight years ago,
it was my father, Gao Yuhai,
who bribed the warehouse manager,
Bai Jiuzhou,
to forge the inventory list,
framing Dacheng Group
for the illegal business operations
that Wending Group should have borne.
Right now,
I am reporting my father, Gao Yuhai,
not only for suspected trafficking
of banned chemical materials,
but also for instructing
his subordinate Feng Shu,
the
fiancé he chose
for
me, to hire a hitman.
To murder the warehouse manager,
Bai Jiuzhou,
who committed perjury for him,
by staging
a traffic accident.
Right now,
I am reporting my father,
Turn it off.
Gao Yuhai,
Turn it off!
for all the evil deeds he has committed.
Turn it off.
Gao Yayan
would rather let her father go to jail
than be apart from you.
What about you?
Fake.
It's fake.
Impossible.
My plan was flawless.
You're all teaming up
to trick me, aren't you?
Fake.
Fake?
It's fake.
Remember?
This is for you.
Are you really giving me
this medal?
Of course
not.
Just lending it to you for a few days.
You dare trick me!
You left it at my house when we were kids.
I never gave it back to you.
Take
it.
Take it.
You take it.
Song Yanfei, look at me.
Take it.
Look at me.
Haven't you always wanted
to be a good director
since you were little?
You even cried
for days when you
accidentally lost it.
Do you remember?
Song Yanfei,
how could you let your life
turn out
like this?
Li Xingchen,
I thought
you would understand me.
I had no choice.
You did.
I didn't.
You can seek legal help.
Ridiculous.
This is ridiculous.
Li Xingchen, this is ridiculous.
If you were me,
you'd do the same.
I'll definitely keep this safe for you.
Li Xingchen,
come back!
Give it to me.
Come back!
Give it back!
Bai Xiaosi,
it's time to confess.
You were at the scene
the night of the October 23 case,
weren't you?
I admit it.
Tell me.
What exactly happened that day?
Come clean.
That day,
Song Yanfei told me
to push the tricycle
to the designated spot,
find a safe place to hide,
and report to him anytime.
Then,
Shen Xi hit Gao Yuhai.
Gao Yuhai just happened
to land right in front of me.
Right at my feet.
Call the police.
Help me.
Gao Yuhai,
no need for the police.
This is karma.
Eight years ago,
You are...
Bai Jiuzhou, the warehouse keeper
in the western suburbs,
was hit and sent to the ER.
He has woken up.
Right?
Hello.
You must be
Bai Jiuzhou's wife.
This is Mr. Gao Yuhai,
Chairman of Wending Group.
He's here specifically to see Bai Jiuzhou.
Hello.
Thank you.
Zhao...
Zhao Wenjuan.
A little token of our appreciation.
Please take it.
No need to be polite.
Just take it.
Thank you.
You shouldn't be thanking us.
We are the ones who should
thank Jiuzhou.
If Jiuzhou hadn't testified for us,
Wending Group
would have really gone under this time.
Fengshu,
perfect timing.
Take
Zhao...
Wenjuan.
to the inpatient department
and pay a 100,000 deposit.
You'll need it
for the hospitalization.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Go ahead.
I'm here for you.
Let's go.
Bai Jiuzhou
has such a beautiful wife.
Why bother?
So stubborn.
Ill-fated.
Xiao Ze, Wang Hao
Jiang Dahai, Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Bai Xiaosi, Liu Xiaolong (Liu Xubai)
Mu Liyan, Chen Yongxia
Bai Jiuzhou, Qin Peng
Gao Yuhai, Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Cast (in stroke order of surnames)
Trace Evidence Police, Kang Hairu
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Little Bai Xiaosi, Zhang Weilun
Investor, Zha Minxin
Li Xingchen's Classmate, Gao Jingman
Extras
Police, Yang Menglin, Wang Yiguo
Xiao Ze's Father, He Meng
Dancers, Liu Yuexin, Yang Jiayue
Friends, Xiao Ba, Niu Dali
Li Xingchen's Classmate,
Tang Tang, Dai Guoming
Secretary, Qian Duoduo
Girl, Ying Ying, Huang Mingfei
Feng Shu's Secretary, Dai Dai
Fleeing Driver, Liu Haohan
Wang Jiasheng
Speaking Police, Wang Zhiguo
Mother, Liu Li
Middle-aged Man, Wang Xinda
Driver Lao Zhao, Wei Hong
Ji Lao Zhao, Wei Hong
Locksmith, Fu Wang
Xiao Ze's Father, Zhou Wen
Xiao Ze's Mother, Pei Xiao
Speaking Girl, Yue Yue
Young Man, Tang Yuye
Female Secretary, Qian Duoduo
Driver
Wounded, Xu Ganggang
Crane Operator, Liu Haitao
Female Teacher, Ai Li
Li Tianjun
Yan's Mother, Zhang Minghui
Male Doctor, Wang Keming
Male Nurse, Wu Zeyu
Speaking Neighbor, Wu Meiling
BBQ Restaurant Guest
Speaking Contestant, Nan Xi, Xu Ziyi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in, Zhao Peng
Jiang Dahai's Stand-in, Zhou Zhen
Taxi Driver, Bai Lei
Lao Zhou, Ren Haizhong
Cashier, Wu Tiantian
Female Police Officer, Wu Lihua
Forensic Doctor, Zhou Wen, Pei Xiao
Execution Doctor, Geng Jie
Cleaner, Liu Li
Streamer, Sun Jialiang
Extra Daqing, Liu Haohan
Hotpot Restaurant Owner, Qin Haitao
Presenters, Sui Dalong, Yu Tianhang
Consultant, Bai Di
Hu Kaichen
Zhang Ningning
Planner, Zhao Feng
Script Planner, Zhang Wanlu
Life Producer, Yin Zhongheng
Line Producer, Hu Huazheng
Finance, Geng Yusa
Key Grip, Liu Yiqing
Kitchen Manager, Yin Xiumei
Chef, Yin Baoxin
Wang Jizhangxiong
Li Xiaojun, Song Shuwei
Niu Yuwang, Wang Yiguo
Xiao Yucai, Liu Xin
Zhang Haiping, Cao Yongjie
Directing Team
Director: Yue Shunming
Director: Xu Yue
Executive Director: Sui Chenggong
Assistant Directors: Tang Yuye, Li Gaoyang
Casting Director: Dai Guoming
Editing Team
Editor: Wu Yingjie
Pre-production Audio Equipment Provided by
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Sound Director: Zhang Kai
Art & Props Team
Executive Art Director: Wang Wenqi
Set Decorator: Zhang Xueqi
Props Director: Yang Xueshan
Props Master: Wu Tai
On-set Supervisor: Hou Yonghao
Props Arrangement: Zhang Li,
Zhang Qingzhong
Camera Team
Camera A Operator: He Yong
Camera A Focus Puller: Yao Yonglei
Camera B Operator: Zhao Shidian
Camera B Focus Puller: Li Chenlong
Camera C Operator: Ma Mingguo
Camera C Focus Puller: Xie Xiaozhong
Camera Assistants: Guo Ruicai, Liu Shihao
Still Photographer: Dong Guiping
Lighting Director: Gao Yun
Lighting Assistants: Zhang Xiaoguang,
Chang Lin
Terigun
Styling Team
Styling Director: Gao Bin
On-set Hair & Makeup Supervisor: Li Zixu
On-set Wardrobe: Zhang Tingting,
Qiu Yaqiong
Beijing This Is Cola Culture
Media Co., Ltd.
Planning Director
Yang Liuting
Media Manager: Yue Yue
Copywriters: Zhang Weirui, Li Ziwei
Video Editors: Wang Jiahui, Miao Wenbo
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-production Supervisor: Wu Wenhui
Colorist: Niu Xuerui
End Credits: Jin Linxin
Trailer Production: Li
Dialogue Editor: Dong Xuebing
Sound Effects Editor: Zhang Xiaoman
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
VFX Execution: Jin Linxin
Compositors: Gao Dong, Wu Yingjie
Shang Chenyao
Beijing Landuo Music
Music Coordinators: Jiang Zheng,
Liu Zining
Female Humming: Ma Qianran
Songs
Lyrics: Yue Shunming
Children's Vocals: Zhang Maolin
Arrangement: Xiao Zhuang
Vocals: Zhang Keying
Lyrics: Bai Yuxiang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Vocals: Xu Yue
Lyrics: Gao Jingman
Arrangement: Wang Anyu
Producer: Xu Yue
Lyrics: Fan Fan
Composer: Xu Yue
Producer: Xu Yue
"The More You Love, The More You Err"
Vocals: Wang Weijia
Arrangement: Zhao Yi
Vocals: Liu Ruixun
Lyricist: Bai Yuxiang
Composer: Zhao Yi
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Special Thanks
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Fangxian Lulingwang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Sinopharm Dongfeng Huaguo Hospital
Dongfang Yuanzhi School,
Maojian District, Shiyan
Hubei Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Mingxin Huizhi Dance Academy
Shiyan Haishuo Loading
and Unloading Machinery Co., Ltd.
Exclusive Social Media Platform
Weibo
Chief Partner Media
Sina Entertainment, Weibo TV, Sina TV
Beijing Sui Brothers Film
and Television Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Co-production Companies
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Songyuan Senchengda Economic
and Trade Co., Ltd.